http://www.chocolate.org/pages/privacy-policy

News & Recipes
By visiting Chocolate.org, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement.
WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT CUSTOMERS DOES CHOCOLATE.ORG GATHER?
For your long-term privacy and security of your credit card, we do not save credit card numbers after orders are complete.
We use other information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future website enhancements for you, improving our products, and communicating with you.
AUTOMATIC INFORMATION
Like many other web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses www.chocolate.org such as the referring page and your IP address.
E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS
To help us improve the quality of our email content, we may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Chocolate.org if your computer supports such capabilities.
Emails sent for promotional purposes are sent ONLY to those users who opt-in to receive them. Every email for this purpose also contains a link to change your email preferences, and/or opt-out.
DOES CHOCOLATE.ORG SHARE THE INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not sell it to others. We share customer information only as described below.
AGENTS
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
BUSINESS TRANSFERS
As we continue to develop our business, we may be acquired by or purchase other businesses. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless the customer consents otherwise).
PROTECTION OF CHOCOLATE.ORG AND OTHERS
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Chocolate.org users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We will not under any condition sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
NO DISCLOSURE WITHOUT YOUR CONSENT
If an unforseen condition ever arises where Chocolate.org wishes to disclose your information to a third party, you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
HOW SECURE IS INFORMATION ABOUT ME?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the payment gateway and credit card company during order processing. We do not save your credit card information on our server after your order is complete.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
WHICH INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?
Chocolate.org gives you access to information about your account and your interactions with Chocolate.org for the limited purpose of updating that information.
WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?
As discussed, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of Chocolate.org features.
CHILDREN
Chocolate.org does not sell products directly to children. If you are under 18, you may purchase products from Chocolate.org only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.
CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS
If you choose to visit www.chocolate.org, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California.
Our business does change, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use may also change. We may email periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you’ll want check our website to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
This document was last updated on January 11, 2019.
help@chocolate.org949398220617302 Daimler St, Unit A, Irvine, CA 92614United States
Copyright © 2020 Chocolate.org.
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
